(Howard:)It's pretty late.
(Howard:)You think I've got time
to run some more simulations
(Howard:)on the cooling system?
(Leonard:)Sure, I'm still figuring out
(Leonard:)the thermo-acoustic expander.
(Sheldon:)Oh, while you do that
(Sheldon:)I am going to pump
cerebral spinal fluid
(Sheldon:)through my brain cells to remove
the metabolic by-products
(Sheldon:)of the day's thoughts.
(Howard:)What?
(Sheldon:)It's called sleep
and it's my bedtime.
(Sheldon:)Nighty-night, y'all.
(Howard:)Hey, hey, hey,
you're not going anywhere.
(Leonard:)We only have two months to
deliver this to the Air Force
(Leonard:)because of you.
(Sheldon:)I know, I was there.
Well, wake up!
(Howard:)We're gonna put in
a lot of late nights.
(Sheldon:)How late?
(Howard:)Well, I don't know,
midnight, 1:00.
(Sheldon:)One o'clock?
(Sheldon:)I'm not a raccoon.
(Howard:)If you're tired,
have some coffee.
(Howard:)What?
You have some coffee.
I am having coffee!
(Sheldon:)And look how irritable
it's making you!
Guys!
(Leonard:)We're not gonna get anything
done if we start fighting.
(Leonard:)Now, can you please try
to soldier through?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)I don't think
I can go much longer.
(Leonard:)It's been three and a half
minutes, wake up!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪